A Guide to the Marshall W. Fishwick Collection, c.1923-1935, 1940s-2006
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series I: Papers
  - Personal Dreams, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Poems, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Publishing Documents & Correspondence, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Articles, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Regionalism Revised, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Prologue, Intro, Etc., n.d. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Devil, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Doom Boom, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Cancer of Culture, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Dance, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - United States Education Foundation in Denmark, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - J. Coleman (Presbyterian), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Depression, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Valley, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - A Sort of Satanic Hardening: Germany 1962, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Lee in Lexington, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Papers From Lexington & Washington and Lee, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Natural Bridge, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - General Lee, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Guardian Angel, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Epigraphs - Introduction, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Lexington (imprints), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Miley Book (press, inc.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Tatnal School, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Wooster, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Scotch Oil Co., n.d. (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Rockfound, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Wallace, "Bigfoot", n.d. (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Rockbridge Country History, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - California Furnace, Iron Works, and Natural Bridge Movie Script, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Schools, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Lee, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Plot, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - General Lee's Photographer, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Rockbridge County - General Information, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Popular Culture / Photos, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Murphy, Blacksburg, Virginia, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Photography, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Photos, Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Poetry 1940s, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Poetry World War II, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Family, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Letters, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Personal/Family, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Personal/Family, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Personal, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Personal Photos, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Personal, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Writings: Cicero and Poetry, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Rome, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 3Rs: Conclusion, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 17th Century Descartes & Burke: PBS Series, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - American Dream, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Autobiography, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Xnty, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cowboy/West, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson and Lee, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Kathy/Global, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Writings: The People & The Masses, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Outline - New Memoirs, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Mss. Pieces Hamorth (Cicero), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - My Books - Promo, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - New Thomas Jefferson, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Pending, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Owen, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Recycle, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - What If?, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - My Best Picture, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Washington, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Popular Culture Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Notes on Popular Culture, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Photos, News Clippings, Etc., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Reloading the Canon (3 Folders), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 26 - 28)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Bottom Line, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Spring Introduction, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Medical Science Waters Analysis, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Mattie Adkins at 90, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Spring Fiction, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sweet Sulphur, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Cavaliers - Horse Joust, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Sweet, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Springs on TV, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - New "VA" Book, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Dreams, 7 Sisters, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Claire White - Green Springs, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - NEH - TV Scripting S.E.C.A., n.d. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - W.VA. Cousing, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Popular Culture, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Survival, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Writings, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Maps. Diagrams, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Forward, Index, Appendices, Etc., n.d. (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - 1940, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Jefferson S. High, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Communication - Lifestyle (Box 29)
  - Shock (Box 30)
  - Art (Box 31)
  - Architecture (Box 32)
  - American Studies & Regionalism (Box 33)
  - American Studies & Regionalism Continued (Box 34)
  - Communication - Function (Box 35)
  - History - Washington & Lee Notes Since Descartes (Box 36)
  - Religion (Box 37)
  - Religion Continued & American Studies (Box 38)
  - History - Since Descartes Continued / Humanities Introduction / History Introduction (Box 39)
  - Sociology & Natural Science (Box 40)
  - Class Notes and Handouts, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Fishwick Works, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Book Reviews, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Popular American Heroes, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - "Cicero Still Speaks" and Interview Release, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - "Wandering in the Ecclesiastical Desert", n.d. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Probing Popular Culture and Call for Book Manuscripts, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Fishwick Information, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - "To Virginia with Love" and Reviews by Fishwick, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Popular Culture, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Supplementary Statement and Fellowship Application, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Virginia and Genealogy, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers Clippings/Articles, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous American Studies, Popular Culture, and Correspondence, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Travels/A.S.S., n.d. (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Style/Lore, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Squibs, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Pending, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - "Pioneers" - P.C.A., n.d. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Lyrics, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Reprints, Essays, Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Summons for Feast Days Reverend Thomas Benett, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Speaking of Virginia, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - 1976 - f, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - 4 Lores = Folk/Fake & Popular/Cyber, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - 1999-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - 2000, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Advance or Retreat, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Conclusion/Autobiography, 1990-1999 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Cowboy, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - East-West, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Future, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Magazines and Journals, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Magazines and Journals, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Popular Culture, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Ornament, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Planner, Maps, and Calenders, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Ideas and Objects, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Popular Culture/Writings, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Williams, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Heroes Chapter 1, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Billy the Kid, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Heroes, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Hero, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Conclusion - Final, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Heroes, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Loose Papers, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Introduction/Conclusion, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Women, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Pope JP 2 - Life, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Heroes - Table of Contents, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Old Joe Clark Folklore - Heroes, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Lee -Bibliography, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Madonna, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Heroes Old and New, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Man and Mouse, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Greece, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Intern People's College Elainore, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Index Cards, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - ENT Whistle, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Lexington Programs, etc., n.d. (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Seabury Conferences, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Richmond, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Chitty, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Pacific School Religion, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Memoirs Inside 20th Century, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - American Popular Public Diplomacy, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Kaine, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Pictures, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Fun and Games, 2004 Election, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Randolph, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Popular Culture, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Different, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Crowd/Mass = Culture, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Nostalgia, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Magazines Scribers, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Cowboy (now girl) !, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - "Jason's Journal", n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Philosophy, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Cicero, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Essays, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Book Photos, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - VITA and Photos, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Red House, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Essays, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Western Virginia (settlement), n.d. (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Navy, Tower Hall, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Pearl, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Fishwick Covers, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Roanoke, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Haworth, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - du Pont, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - New Poems, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Amy Rentner - 359, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Cicero - ADD, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Poetry, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Haworth, 2006-2007 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Literary, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Poetry, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Nostalgia, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Poetry, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Early Poems, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Poems, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Poems, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Research, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Application and Correspondence, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Jordan Clippings, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Jordan: Bridge Builder, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Jordan Architect, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Jordan Accomplishments, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Research/Writing Stono, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Writings/Virginia, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - William Weaver, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - "Ideas and Objects", n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Speaking of Virginia Complete, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Speaking of Virginia, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Medium/Messiah Complete, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - "To Virginia with Love", n.d. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - "Lady Eightball" Final, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - "Ideas and Objects" Master Copy, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - "In Search of Cox's Bazar" Final, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - "Far Out", n.d. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - "Ideas and Objects", n.d. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Railroad, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Europe Travels, 1960-1969 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - United States Information Agency - The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - International Communication Agency, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - International Communication Agency, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - United Kingdom, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Rome, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Rome, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - India, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - India & United States Citizenship and Immigration Services & Brown, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Bangladesh, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Bangladesh, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - France, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Italy and Summer, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Bangladesh, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Bangladesh Pictures, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - India, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Europa, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Italy - Europe, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Poland - Scanlan, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - CU/EE, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Luxembourg, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Europe - Fulbright Trip to Denmark, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Photography, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Roma, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Awards, Commendations, etc., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous 4.0!, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Wemyss/WWL -, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Laird, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Repairs and Deeds, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Saturday Review Articles, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Fishwick HW, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Emeritus, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Memorabilia, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - 1970-1976, 1970-1976 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - MWF/Conclusion & 20th Century 77!, 1923-2000 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - P.C. Best Students, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Tech, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - To Bind, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Stan Squibs, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Essays, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Fads, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Cicero, Trisha, and Release Forms, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Pop Poetry, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - P. Book, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - In Memoriam MW, 1929-1984 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Vita, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Fishwick Books, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Disney, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Newspapers, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Rover Boys, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - American Studies, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Common Culture & Great Tradition - Bound Copy, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Cicero - Bound Copy, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Searching For Cicero - Bound Copy, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - God Pumpers: For Preaching in America - Working Draft, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Seven Pillars of Popular Culture- Bound Copy, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Italy - Bound Copy, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Lady Eight-Ball - Bound Copies, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Far Out in the Promised Land - Work in Progress, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - In Search of Cox's Bazar - Bound Copy, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - God Pumpers - with Footnotes, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Personal/Family Letters and Photos, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Published Journals and "The West and the American Imagination", n.d. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - American Studies Research Program Progress Report, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Winterthur, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - American Artifacts in Britain, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Tatnall Visiting Scholar Program, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Cox's Bazar, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - American Studies Research Program Progress Report Volume II, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Articles, Journals, Magazines, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Publications and Writings, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Reprints, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Fishwick Publications and Writings, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Fishwick Publications and Writings and Westermann Publication, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Fishwick Writings, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Right Forms for American Studies, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Fishwick Writings and Programs, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Saturday Reviews, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Journals, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Journal Publications, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Journal Publications, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Diocese of Southwestern Virginia - Living History Series, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Speech Reprints, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1949 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1989 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Memorabilia, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Photos and Letters, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Photos Book/Research Information, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and Personal Pieces, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence and Personal Pieces, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 2006-2007 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Photos Family and Friends, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - New Photos, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Myths and Dreams, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - My West - Far East ?, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Popular Religion, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Washington and Lee, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Hughes Quotes, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Washington and Lee, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Washington and Lee, 1950-1959 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Lexington Gazette, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - The Church, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Marquis de Chastellux visits Valley, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - 1800-1810, 1800-1810 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - 1760-1780, 1760-1780 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Kosnic - Kirby France, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - J/B Adams/Hughes, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - 1810-1820, 1810-1820 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Margaret Graham Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - The Springs and the Story of Bath County, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - 1949, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Fishwick Abroad, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Springlore in Virginia, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Virginia - Endangered ?, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Speaking of Virginia, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Preface, etc., n.d. (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - New Icons, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Hackers, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Style and Lore, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Nailed Down - Coming Loose, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - London, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Further Reading, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Bangladesh, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence with Other Schools, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Fulbright, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Junkin, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Travel Introduction, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Horses, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - To Add, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Cyburbia: Myth and Reality, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Passage to India, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Fishwick Early Years, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Fishwick at 75, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Virginia: A Cultural History, 1902-1941 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Yale Years, 1946-1949 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson Senior High Yearbook, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Washington and Lee Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Fishwick Reprints, Articles, Poems, etc., n.d. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Fishwick Family Scrapbook, 1923-1943 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Dreams, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Religion, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - In Search of Cox's Bazar, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - More In Search of Cox's Bazar, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Lady Eightball Draft, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Art and Communication, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Reviews and Writings, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Monger-Lore, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Culture Concept, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Culture and Anthropology Introduction, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Fall 2003, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Popular Culture Materials, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Lady Eightball, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Popular Culture and Art, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Writings and Correspondence, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Old Tom and the Seven Sisters, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Growing Up and Moving Out Draft, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Writings, Publisher Information, and Popular Culture, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Writings Related to Cicero/Rome, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Writings, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - What I Know About de WAH, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Washington and Lee Years - Scrapbook, 1949-1959 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Wemyss - Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Dillon - Scrapbook, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Poland - Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Letter Volume 1 - Bound, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Letters Volume 2 - Bound, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Renewal, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Post-Modern, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous - To Do, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Technology, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Glut, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Technology, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Post-Modern, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Myths/Makers, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Van, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Van Auken, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Quotes, Bibliography, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Introduction, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - New Introduction, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Natural Bridge, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Tradition, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Introduction "I luv", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Popular War, CWII, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - 9/11, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - To File Later, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Heroes/Celebrities, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 19)